Do you find these comfortable with clothes
?
Yes.  Papa himself is getting uncomfortable without any
reason.
Hi friends, welcome back to my channel.
How are you all having fun?  So I am back
in Mumbai.  We have come to Mumbai for
my dental work.  If not today then tomorrow
how will you be able to see my smile.  Isn't it,
Papa?
What?
I was matching the color.
Now even father has started taking skin care.
Look, look at Papa's face.   That's
ok.  So today I am going to give you a very
big surprise.
I will give you a very wonderful gift.  Will remember this Father's Day gift.
Come on,
why would you give me a gift?  I will
give you a gift, right?   Let us go.   The opposite is happening
here.  But first we're going to go up to do the
eyebrows.
Look how much my eyebrows have grown.  So
I'm going to go get my eyebrows done first.  And let
me show you my dress.  One
second.  wait.  Look at this.
[Song voice]
It's so cool, Mummy and I have
twinned.  Mummy is also wearing a red coloured
top.  We both red red I will
go now.
Papa is not able to open even one door.
come soon.
Look guys, I'm here with my eyebrows peeled off.
How does my mouth feel?  Whenever I get my
eyebrows done, I feel as if
my face has completely changed.  Look at this.
Mummy.
Look guys, what is going on with them.
Hey, this is not Husband Day.  It's Father's Day.
So what?
Yes.
Come on, come on, let's do some
shopping, if we come to Mumbai then it doesn't happen like this,
guys, is there a husband's day, is there a husband's day
or not,
tell me in the comments, then there must be a
wife's day too, then I don't know whether it happens or
not, come on,
see, cut the photo right now,
these people again start fighting,
ask to take the photo,
these people fight on this very thing, what should I
say, what did I just say to you, tell me what
I just said to you,
wherever I go, I start Doraemon.
I feel like Doraemon is going to be
my son-in-law.  [ __ ],
man [laughs]
because she just won't let go of Doraemon.
If Doraemon were a human being, I would definitely make him my son-in-law.
Yes done.  Let's go now.
Hey, go from behind.   Guys
, we're off to go shopping.
Now that I have come to Mumbai, I will
go to the mall here and do some great shopping and will
also shop for Papa.  Father's Day
special.   Guys, look,
we have reached the mall.   First of all
we are going to go
shopping for clothes in Judeo.  Whenever
I go to such malls, I feel
incomplete and empty because
Papa does not accompany me.  Right now
Papa should understand that he has to come with me.
I have become used to it like this.  Papa
walks like this, so I am used to holding hands like this.
And now you know what the feeling is.
[Music]
[Music] First of all,
we'll go shopping for Papa.
Look, we have reached the gents
section.  We will get cool clothes for Papa from
here.
No, it is like that.  What are you looking at, mom?  Loose
jeans.  Yes, these days such baggy jeans are
trending.  I am already wearing one.
Look,
yes, such loose clothes are in fashion these days,
Papa.  These ones are cool in white and black.  You
can take the white one.  It is torn.   I will
also buy a full printed T-shirt for Papa.
Papa doesn't wear printed t-shirts like that.
But still we will take it.   I
need a plain t-shirt.
But we will take it.   Will
take it because of this.
Because of this.  Yes.  Look at his dressing sense.
But my father's dressing sense is not that
bad.
Ok.
Yes.  Yes, look, this is trending like this right now,
okay, I will buy it, friend,
take it, that's right, you check the size etc.,
hey, I have seen it with my eyes, it is clear, wow, nice,
what are you saying, mom, mom has
also found some really cool clothes, look, this
shirt is so cool in white color, we are
looking at all the clothes in white only,
hey, we will find a partner for this there,
yes, by the way, what was I saying, let papa finish his
shopping, then we
girls will do our shopping comfortably, because what
if we do shopping first, our
shopping takes time, papa had
bought white colored pants.  Look at that, we are
taking this green colored shirt.  Nowadays,
such colors look very nice in non-contrast.
Looks stylish too.
Okay, my shopping is done, now do yours.
Just
look at this one, how nice it is, right?
How is your mother?
What happened?
Look, move it aside.
You are going to wear one already.
This is the elastic one.
But if it is any color then take another one.
Come to the makeup section.
I really like the makeup here.
Look at this lipstick.  I am looking for a little lighter color
in lipstick shades.
Look, he handed me such a mobile phone,
it was pink in colour and everyone
thinks that this mobile phone is mine and this
pink coloured mobile phone, all of them look straight
towards my face.   Is there any
guarantee that all girls
test on such hands only?  Tell me please.
I have no guarantee about this.  And even
if someone has not tested it by applying it on such a photo,
then how will we know?
How can that be known?  Now let me
keep it like this, look
what is mom taking here?  show.  These slippers,
mom, disappeared for two minutes.  She went
away from us.  Mom quickly finished all the shopping.
Show me what you have taken?  This is a
sleeper.  And we have taken this step.
And I have bought it for your gym.
Yes, see how serious my mother is about my gym.
Look how cool this
is.   You have to
wear it like this while doing gym.  Correct.   The
shoes are good.  Take it, take it, take it.
Papa is forcing me to buy shoes for the gym.   Is
n't this good?
Is good.  The color is good.  He takes it.   That's
ok.  I took this.
Ok.  Guys, look, I
like these slippers.  It is cool and
comfortable too.  In this, mother has chosen this colour.
See which one looks better
?
Which one is comfortable?
That one is the same size as this one.   That's
for you,
yes mom has bought this for him.  Look,
Papa is paying the bill in the back and we are going to do some
shopping.
Meaning to see.  Mummy's my funda.  Let's
see what I'm going for.  Right now
we are looking at earrings.  C Guys Wow
we have to move ourselves.  It is not
rotating on its own.
Wow guys, look how beautiful this dress
is.  Should I show you, it's cool, right?  It looks
very beautiful as well.  Its color is also very
nice.  Take it.  Should I take it?  Let's see its size.
Look how cool this is.
He is also my father.
Papa is not saying anything.
This one
is M size.  I also like this tube top.
Look, it is yellow in colour.
How cool it is.  By the way, I have
bought one of those pink dresses.  We
will see more here.  It looks cool.  Wow.
Hi.   Yes, yes.
Guys, look how amazing this bikini top
looks.  Isn't it?  Below this, there is this
loose sash to wear.  Butt
inside it is like this.  Look, the whole set is like this.
This entire set is like a bikini.  Wow,
isn't that right girl?
This one is also so beautiful.
This pink one is also so cute.  Is carefree.
C This bikini top here.  And these shots are
perfect, right?  What a cool dude.  Look, this one
is also cool.
Wow.  Look, I have wooed mom.  And
I am thinking of buying this bikini.  The
whole set is visible.
Yes, it is completely set.  This is the top and this
is the bottom.  These are shorts and this
is a shirt over it.  Complete set.  Now I don't know where
I will wear it but it will be fun.  I have taken it.
Collection should be done, right?   A
collection should be made.  Mom put it right.
Thanks.  May everyone have such a cool mom.   But if I
wear this bikini, I will wear it with them only.
Put it.  This one is also a bikini set.  Look
how cool it is.  Isn't it?  It is very cool and the colour is also
good.  Look, I have come here to
see perfumes.  I love
buying perfumes.
This one is good.
And another one for
exercise.
Then why are you fighting?
But it belongs to the
PT children of the school.
No.   It
is very dark.
No.   It feels
good.  Papa
wears clothes like this.  I don't feel any PT-VT.
Then what is it?  That will not be worn by children and girls in school, it is for
PT,
this size will be available for
primary, yes it is a small size,
bring the M size, no no,
this will be available, let's go
quickly,
yes okay, I have bought a perfume, the
vanilla flavoured one, I am going now, let's keep
Papa aside to see the cosmetics, let's see if
anything
new has come, I want to see a light shade lipstick
in a very light nude,
yes matte and creamy
matte creamy both,
what are all these
tools,
Papa
hardware and tools guys,
I bought two shades of lipstick.
One is this first one and the other is this
first one over here.  I have bought both of these.   I do
n't know, mom has disappeared, friend.
And it is very risky to leave mommy open like this.
Mom is there, she will do a lot of shopping
then.  Look at this.  Here it is.  Let us go.
Look at this, I have such a beautiful and cute coaching centre.
Wow, right?
Yes, it is cool.  The color is also cool.
Hey, stop it.  Stop it.  Don't you cross the limits
?  Look how cool this one is.
You also brought the same school dress.   I do
n't have school dress, Papa.  This is fashion.
Understand, do this also.  What a beautiful dress
I brought.  Proud of me.
You just keep increasing the bill and don't do anything else.
So good clothes are available here in Mumbai.   Do
n't you find yourselves like this?
No.
What are you talking about?
Fashionable.  It is so fashionable.
And this is me.
Full with a bag.
This with the bag.  This is full with full bag.
They are still shopping and it is not done yet.   It is still
very much ongoing.  They keep shopping until the entire bill is
made.
Guys you know we had come to buy this one piece
which I liked very much from outside.
But we did shopping worth Rs 10,000 and the
bill came to Rs 10,000.  This is how we are.
Guys, we are done shopping from here.  Now
we are going to Infinity Mall.  I have
a surprise for Papa.
But I was saying, do
you find these clothes comfortable?  Yes.
Papa himself is getting uncomfortable without any reason.
Hey, a towel can't be handled properly here, friend.
So what are you talking about?
Hey, this is cool, look guys.
Then this must also be a talent.   Yes.
Look guys, we have reached Infinity.
Will shop here now.
So guys, the gift is that I'm gifting my dad an
Apple Watch on Father's Day [screaming sound].
Happy Papa, I am
using it for the first time, so I will see it after using it.
Yes, Papa was saying for a long time that
he does not want an Apple Watch.  I
need an Apple Watch.  So finally we have come to
buy Apple Watch.
See what you like.  This is the
latest model, isn't it?  Try wearing this and see
how it feels on your hand.
Look, the Apple Watch is suiting Papa's hand so well.
Wow, to
wear it on the left hand.  This is on the
right hand side,
right on the left side, so this is it,
look I got Kavya's subscribers here
in the mall, what was she
saying a lot, tell me now,
actually my Shraddha is yours, she likes you a lot,
thank you,
hi,
she remembered me in the morning itself after watching my vlog and
I met her in the evening,
yes and my mother was saying that she has grown so
big, still she is watching her vlog,
you also do something
and today I finally got her, thank
you, thank
you,
what did you say, it was my
dream, mom, Kavya didi, you do the
canfest
today in Mumbai, didi,
how good, she
said, satrat, Sandhya met, bye
Vanshika,
bye ma'am, bye bye, the
girl does not lose, we also watch with her,
thank you, this is
not your brother, no,
this is Nagesh who came from work,
or father, you guys meet like this, it
feels very nice.   Thank
you.  You are also good, ma'am.
All of you, my subscribers, who
meet me, I feel very good.
And when you tell me that you like my
blogs very much.  You have to
meet me.  When you manifest,
I feel very much like this after hearing this.  The heart becomes
happy.  Thank you.
Hi Guys.  So now it is the next day
and this may not be my last video
because after this I am going to have
a small dental operation and I don't know whether
I will be able to talk after that or not,
then I will have to wear a mask
and I don't know what my face is going to look like.
I am feeling very scared
and we have just come to a South Indian
restaurant to have breakfast
because after this I might have to
eat liquid.  So this is my last solid
meal.  Well, the videos will keep coming.  You don't
worry.  I am just thinking of taking a break for
a few days because I don't know
how my teeth will look.  Mom, please
see my face for the last time.  Look how my teeth look.
Show it in the camera.
Look at my teeth.
How many are inside?  Look at this one, this one.
It's very deep inside.   I do
n't know what is going to happen to me today.
It's inside.  Because of this, China looks a little different.
So how will it happen now?  What will happen.  I am also
feeling scared.  Therefore, we will feed him to his heart's content, whatever
he wants.  Then after that you
can drink liquid.   If you have
pain in your teeth or you have sensitive teeth, then may
everything be fine with you.
All the best guys.
Today is a big day for Kavya.  Life
is about to change.
Yes, life and teeth too.
What is?
He is always drunk,
leave him alone, ignore him guys.  Look at this guys.  Here
is our breakfast Onion Uttapam.  This is Idli
Vada and Masala Dosa.  We came back after having this breakfast.  I am feeling
a little nervous right now.
I am feeling very scared right now.  Let us go.
Now let's see what happens with Ka.
I'm also scared, Guys.
But I am not telling this.  I am
telling this.  Come on, nothing happens.
Everything will be fine.  I don't know what's going to happen to my teeth now.  I do
n't know how my face will look.  I might go
on bed rest.  I couldn't talk for a few days.
But don't worry.  We went on a trip to Goa with my aunt.
His videos will keep coming.  So
quickly like the video and subscribe to the channel
and enjoy Goa videos.
[music]